Mighty Little Defenders 11 – New Wild Cosmos.
The Heart Knot
Episode 11
Today, with heavy hearts,
we announce the devastating news
that His Majesty the King and His Highness Prince Sparky
have been eaten by the monster.
What? Even the Prince was eaten?
It’s over. The Bulala Kingdom is over.
Don’t panic everyone, Master Quan is still here
The future of Bulala Kingdom is guarded by Master Quan
He will never let anyone be harmed by monsters
Please believe in Master Quan and support Master Quan
Master Quan the New King
Do we support Master Quan?
I support Master Quan to become the new King
With Master Quan here, we don’t have to be afraid of the monster.
With Master Quan as the King, our Bulala Kingdom will be saved.
King Quan
support King Quan
King Quan King Quan King Quan
You still have some value, I can’t deal with you now
What’s wrong
I did a lot of bad embroidery and Father scolded me for wasting Bulala.
It’s okay to waste some Bulala on something you like.
follow me
Here you are
Use with confidence
Uncle supports you
Thank you, Uncle. I will support you in the future.
I thought you would understand me
I didn’t expect you to be like him
My dear brother, I won this time
From now on I am the new King of Bulala Kingdom
Everything is decided by me and all Bulala belong to me
we are still alive
we are indeed alive
Monster
Help
Calm down
But it ate us
Are you actually eating us to save us?
This is
These must have been done by Uncle again
But where did such a big Little Cutie come from?
There is no such monster in our world
I don’t know what day I jumped out of the cave.
It turns out you also came from the rifts
go home
In fact, we also come from the world on the other side of the rift.
Are you leaving now?
We have one more important thing to do
It must be resolved before going home.
But this is only our—
Don’t forget that we are partners
Thanks
Of course we help our partners when they are in trouble
Do you want to help too?
I’m so touched
Thank you so much
But the strange power in Uncle’s body is too strong
We are no match for him
Actually, it’s not like there’s no way at all.
Look
The King arrives
What a beautiful and long robe.
So beautiful, so luxurious
Mom, our Bulala has been confiscated
Why does the King still have so many Bulala?
And it was made into such a long and beautiful robe
From today on I am your new King
From now on, everyone must diligently offer
Monster, monster
Monster, run away, help
Help, run away
We’ve already handed over Bulala, so why is the monster still here?
Look, there’s someone on top of the monster
Brother, stop it
What
that is
No way
It’s the King and Prince Sparky
Weren’t you eaten by the monster? Why are you still alive?
It’s not a monster, it’s obviously a docile Little Cutie.
Shut up, you are colluding with the monster
Catch them quickly
Brother, you use the monster to create panic
Take the opportunity to collect everyone’s Bulala
In fact, everything is to satisfy your own selfish desires
You have never thought about your people at all.
It turns out that we collected Bulala day and night
Just to satisfy his selfish desires
you don’t deserve it
Don’t go there, everyone
Do you think you can win with more people?
Only the powerful can win
No
don’t hurt them
Let’s go
Okay
Dare to confront me head-on, overestimating your own abilities
Uncle, it’s too late to stop now
Stop talking nonsense
caught
Brother, I’m sorry
Only by grasping your Heart Knot can we prevent you from making mistakes
We Bulala people all have a core called Heart Knot
This core is our weakness
But everyone’s Heart Knot is in different locations
I know where his Heart Knot is
So despicable
Brother, pull back from the brink and look back
It’s disgusting that you win every time
Give you
Got you
You are too extravagant and wasteful. You see your brother is very frugal.
You’re wrong, it’s you, it’s you
Why are we quarreling again?
There is no overnight feud between brothers
From now on, if you encounter a problem,
just let it sit overnight
and solve it together tomorrow.
This trial is very simple
Whoever finds the best Bulala will inherit the throne
Father, I found the biggest Bulala
The biggest is the best
What did you find?
I found Golden Bulala
Golden Bulala. Isn’t that a legend?
You can’t find Golden Bulala
I really found it
Father, Brother
Please come with me
Did you hear that? This is Golden Bulala.
Ridiculous. This is not Golden Bulala at all
I’m not convinced
Why did you get the throne and the robes and not me?
unfair
I also made a robe myself
I found out that Bulala can calm the monster
We just have to offer Bulala regularly
No, it will make life difficult for residents
I decided to tame it myself
Be good, we are good people too
Brother, this monster has been tamed by me
We can tell everyone that we don’t have to be afraid anymore
Can’t let you succeed
Very docile
The King is mighty The King is wise
Do you think you understand my Heart Knot?
You don’t even know what my Heart Knot is about
To be continued